https://fourgates.com/terms-of-use-1/

Sarongs
Kimonos (Cotton, Silk, Vintage)
FAQ's
Green Conscious policyGiving / PhilanthropyPrivacy policyTestimonialsShipping & ReturnsTerms of UseWholesale
News n Events
EducationGreat InvocationTen Virtues of Burning IncenseAffirmation of a Disciple
Site Information
Loading... Please wait...
FAQ's
Green Conscious policyGiving / PhilanthropyPrivacy policyTestimonialsShipping & ReturnsTerms of UseWholesale
News n Events
EducationGreat InvocationTen Virtues of Burning IncenseAffirmation of a Disciple
Sarongs
Kimonos (Cotton, Silk, Vintage)
Welcome to Four Gates
By accessing the website, you warrant and represent to the website owner that you are legally entitled to do so and to make use of information made available via the website.
This site may contain other proprietary notices and copyright information from third party companies, publishers, individual not directly affiliated with Four Gates and all copyright laws both domestic, and foreign must be observed. Information on this site may contain technical inaccuracies or typographical errors. Information, including product pricing and availability, may be changed or updated without notice. Four Gates and its subsidiaries reserve the right to refuse service, terminate accounts, and/or cancel orders in its discretion, including, without limitation, if Four Gates or any affiliated company believes that customer conduct violates applicable law or is harmful to the interests of Four Gates and its subsidiaries.
The trademarks, service marks and logos displayed on this website are the exclusive property of Four Gates, affiliated companies and our parent company, and are protected under U.S. and international trademark law. Use of any of these marks without prior written permission of our company is strictly prohibited.
The design, images, text content and overall layout contained in this website are protected under U.S. And international law as copyrighted materials. Anyone who claims, displays, reproduces copies or creates derivative works for commercial or noncommercial purposes without the prior written permission from Four Gates and our parent company is in violation of the copyright laws and is liable for copyright infringement to the greatest extent of the law.
We make no warranties or representations as to the accuracy or completeness of the content of this website. Prices and product offers are subject to change. Four Gates will not be liable for any damages, consequential or otherwise, arising out of the access or use of this site, or any linked sites.
Third-Party Content
This website contains content supplied by parties other than Four Gates. Any opinions, advice, statements, services, offers, or other information or content expressed or made available by such third parties, including information providers and users, are those of the respective author(s) or distributor(s) and not of Four Gates. Our company, nor any third-party provider of information guarantees the accuracy, completeness, or usefulness of any content, nor its merchantability or fitness for any particular purpose. In many instances, the content available through our company represents the opinions and judgments of the respective third-party information provider or user, and not of Four Gates.
Privacy Policy
Use of personal information that you may submit to us through this web site, or any other is governed by the Four Gates Privacy Policy, which states that when you submit your information, we agree not to sell, rent or trade it outside of our company. Our company does have other divisions however, such as,, www.EulogyToday.com, www.WeddingVowsToday.com, www.LoveMattersMost.net, and www.AskaSpiritualTeacher.com and others under development.
This website may contain links to other websites. Please be aware that our websites is not responsible for the privacy practices of other websites.
Disclaimer of Warranty; Limitation of Liability
(a) Each user expressly agrees that use of this website is at his or her sole risk. Neither Four Gates, nor any of its respective affiliates, employees, agents, third-party content providers, technical providers, or licensors, if any ("companies") warrant that this website will be uninterrupted or error free, nor do they make any warranty as to the results that may be obtained from use of this website or as to the accuracy, reliability, or content of any information, service, or merchandise provided through Four Gates, or its content providers.
(b) This website is provided on an "as is" basis without warranties of any kind, either express or implied, including but not limited to warranties of title or implied warranties of merchantability or fitness for a particular purpose, other than those warranties which are implied by and incapable of exclusion, restriction or modification under the laws applicable hereunder.
(c) The disclaimers of liability contained herein apply to any damages or injury caused by any failure of performance, error, omission, interruption, deletion, defect, delay in operation or transmission, computer virus, communication line failure, theft or destruction or unauthorized access to, alteration of, or use of records or material, whether for breach of contract, tortious behavior, negligence, or under any other cause of action. Each user specifically acknowledges that Four Gates is not liable for the defamatory, offensive or illegal conduct of third parties, including other users and that the risk of injury from the foregoing rests entirely with each user.
(d) In no event will Four Gates, or the companies or any person or entity involved in creating, producing, or distributing this website be liable for any direct, indirect, incidental, special, or consequential damages arising out of the use of or inability to use this website or out of the breach of any warranty.
(e) Four Gates, neither endorses nor is responsible for the accuracy or reliability of any opinion, advice, or statement on this website, nor for any offensive, defamatory, or obscene posting made on the service by anyone. Under no circumstances will Four Gates be liable for any loss or damage caused by a user's reliance on information obtained through the content and/or any postings on this website. It is the responsibility of each user to evaluate the accuracy, completeness, or usefulness of any information, opinion, advice, or other content available through and from this website.
(f) Four Gates, does not endorse, warrant or guarantee any product or service offered by a third-party through the service and will not be a party to or in any way monitor any transaction between any user and third-party providers of products or services. As with the purchase of a product or service through any medium or in any environment, each user should use his or her best judgment and exercise caution where appropriate.
(g) Each user specifically acknowledges that in no event will Four Gates, or the companies, nor any of their respective employees or agents be liable for any direct, indirect, incidental, special, or consequential damages arising out of (I) the use by such user of any browser owned or operated by any party and/or (II) the downloading of any software owned or operated by any third-party in connection with the service.
Conflict of terms
If there is a conflict or contradiction between the provisions of these website terms and conditions and any other relevant terms and conditions, policies or notices, the other relevant terms and conditions, policies or notices which relate specifically to a particular section or module of the website shall prevail in respect of your use of the relevant section or module of the website.
Indemnification
Each user agrees to defend, indemnify, and hold harmless Four Gates, and the Companies, its affiliates, and their respective directors, officers, employees, and agents from and against all claims and expenses, including attorneys' fees, arising out of the use of this website by such user, or as otherwise set forth herein.
Special Admonitions for International Use
Recognizing the global nature of this website and Internet, each user agrees to comply with all local rules regarding on line conduct and acceptable content. Specifically, each user agrees to comply with all applicable laws regarding the transmittal of technical data exported from the United States or the country in which such user resides.
Please note that we may revise our above policy as the content on our site continues to change.
Thank you for the opportunity to be of service. Our support, good wishes and prayers are with you.
About Us
FAQ's
Green Conscious policyGiving / PhilanthropyPrivacy policyTestimonialsShipping & ReturnsTerms of UseWholesale
News n Events
EducationGreat InvocationTen Virtues of Burning IncenseAffirmation of a Disciple
Kimonos (Cotton, Silk, Vintage)
Join Our NewsLetter!
Get the latest news and promotions!
Need Help?
1-480-905-7113
FOLLOW US ON
FacebookTwitterYouTubeRSS
Copyright © 2020 Four Gates. All Right Reserved.
Powered by BigCommerce
